Contact

erickodlc@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ericko-de-la-cruz-5b0647147 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java

Unix

Bash

Ericko de la Cruz

A student of lifelong learning

NCR - National Capital Region, Philippines

Summary

A dude specializing in systems analysis and maintenance, especially in Linux/UNIX. I currently maintain AllProfits, a core banking web app, for FIS Global PH.

Outside work, I have interests in health, fitness, business and technology.

Specialties:

Development: Java, C, Perl, SQL, Oracle, SoapUl, Maven, GIT,

SVN, Unix, Bash, Web Services Front End : JavaFX, Javascript

Experience

FIS

Programmer Analyst II February 2018 - Present

Smart Communications, Inc.
EAI Software Development Analyst
June 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 9 months)
NCR - National Capital Region, Philippines

Upwork

Freelance Software Developer October 2016 - November 2017 (1 year 2 months)

Took on Java freelance projects

Uber

Partner/Driver
December 2015 - May 2016 (6 months)

NCR - National Capital Region, Philippines

USANA Health Sciences Independent Associate - Level 1 Director March 2012 - May 2016 (4 years 3 months)

Xybersolutions, Inc Senior Mobile Developer May 2011 - October 2014 (3 years 6 months)

STI

Assistant Instructor June 2010 - March 2011 (10 months)

Education

De La Salle University - Manila
Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2006 - 2010)